

NGUYÊN THANH TRÀ

Food Service Category Staff

🗣 số 77 đường 24, Phường Bình Trị Đông B, Quận Bình Tân, Tp HCM

• 0916935621

Thanh Trà 🖸 Nguyễn Thanh Trà

About me

With more than 5 years of working in different service industry jobs, from F&B, technology software business, general accounting and food business, there are different lessons learned. Although my major is Food Technology, with the spirit of not being afraid to learn and a serious attitude to learning, I believe I can absorb the necessary knowledge and complete the job well as well as perform the tasks, assigned tasks in the job position. The goal in the next 3 to 5 years is to become a position specialist and advance to the position of team leader.

Education

Saigon University of Technology

Food Technology

2015 - 2020

Average - Good

Work Experiences

Hai Dang Food Production Joint Stock Company

Sales Officer

05/2024 - 09/2024

- Customer care (coffee chain, CVS: Ministop/Circle K VN/GS25 VN)
- Handle customer complaints, send information to relevant departments, build agree on how to handle/solve the problems customers are facing. Send customer feedback emails, propose appropriate handling/solutions for all parties.
- Combine R&D to develop new products
- Deploy daily product production information for each chain and new product information to the factory.
- Receive notifications from customers and redeploy related processes from customers: delivery-receipt of goods, opening new products, stopping product sales or stores stopping sales to promptly notify relevant parties.
- Receive daily orders and make delivery documents to the warehouse/store of the supermarket system.
- Support management of records, procedures, inventory of goods, packaging.
- Market research, visit existing stores in the market, monitor and analyze new product trends.
- Draft and archive documents, contracts with customers/suppliers.
- Make reports as required by direct management.

Tho Phat Food Processing Company Limited

Order Processing Staff

09/2023 - 05/2024

- Plan, execute, control the arrangement, create orders and send information to relevant planning departments. Arrange transportation plans, process documents for goods, delivery and receipt services according to customer requirements.
- Handle problems arising during the delivery process.

- Check mail, respond to mail from supermarkets ordering to suppliers
- Receive orders, print orders, make delivery records
- Issue value-added invoices for purchasing units
- Calculate wages and salaries for workers
- Make sales contracts, apply for veterinary licenses for delivery
- Draft and archive documents, contracts with customers/suppliers.
- Receive orders to purchase raw materials from the factory, make orders to suppliers

IPOS.vn Joint Stock Company

Sales staff

03/2021 - 04/2022

- Practice market sales.
- Telesale every day. Self-study negotiation skills, deal with suitable contracts.
- Demo the features to customers and provide solutions suitable for the customer's business model.
- Go to implementation (set up equipment, train customers). Contact support, customer care to create connections for the next cooperation.
- Receive customer feedback to process quickly, take care of customers after signing the contract.
- Achievements: sign many sales contracts, close contracts for high-value brand chains. go to a higher level.

Phuc Long Heritage Corporation

Fulltime Staff - Bartender

09/2019 - 02/2021

- Receive orders from cashiers, process drinks according to the company's drink recipes to ensure product quality and service quality in accordance with company regulations.
- Trained in operations, departments, work positions in the store, new products, preliminary processing, control of raw materials of the bar.
- Achievements: Trained and guided in professional operations of each department. Upgraded to Keystaff

VN Tea Coffee Trading Service Joint Stock Company

Keystaff

01/2017 - 04/2019

- Keystaff receives and processes customer orders to assist the departments
- operating in the store in case the staff cannot handle it in time.
- Receive direct feedback from customers at the store during the shift,
- · if within the scope of handling, it will be processed for the customer immediately, otherwise, it will be transferred
- to the higher management department.
- Achievements: Trained and guided in professional operations of each department. Promoted to a higher position -Supervisor

Skills -

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Excel, Word , Outlook: **** SAP *** - Good communication skills, easy to listen to voice, clear pronunciation, easy to interact and integrate, adapt quickly to different environments. Ability to work in teamwork, negotiate, and solve problems.

Languages - English

Reading ****
Writing ****
Speaking ****
Listening ***